suncoastparts.com 2019-03-04

# Suncoast Porsche Parts & Accessories: Privacy Policy

We know that you care how your information is used, and we appreciate your trust that we will use it carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting us, you are accepting the privacy policy described below.

### What Personal Information Do We Collect?

#### Information You Provide

We receive and store information you enter. For example, when you search for or buy a product or service, or when you supply information such as your address, phone number or credit card. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our website, and communicating with you. In addition, if you choose, we may share your information with other companies who provide goods or services that you are interested in. Please see the "opt-in/opt-out" selection in Section 4 of this policy.

#### Cookies

Like many websites, we use "cookies". Cookies are small programs that we transfer to your hard drive that allow us to recognize you and to provide you with a customized shopping experience. If you do not want us to use cookies, you can easily disable them by going to the toolbar of your web browser, and clicking on the "help"button. Follow the instructions that will prevent the browser from accepting cookies, or set the browser to inform you when you receive a new cookie.In addition, you may visit this and other websites anonymously through the use of utilities provided by other private companies. 

#### The Cookies We Set

· Account related cookies - If you create an account with us then we will use cookies for the management of the signup process and general administration. These cookies will usually be deleted when you log out however in some cases they may remain afterwards to remember your site preferences when logged out. 

· Login related cookies - We use cookies when you are logged in which prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page. These cookies are typically removed or cleared when you log out to ensure that you can only access restricted features and areas when logged in. 

· Email newsletters related cookies - This site offers newsletter or email subscription services and cookies may be used to remember if you are already registered and whether to show certain notifications which might only be valid to subscribed/unsubscribed users. 

· Survey related cookies - From time to time we offer user surveys and questionnaires to provide you with interesting insights, helpful tools, or to understand our user base more accurately. These surveys may use cookies to remember who has already taken part in a survey or to provide you with accurate results after you change pages. 

· Forms related cookies - When you submit data to through a form such as those found on contact pages or comment forms cookies may be set to remember your user details for future correspondence. 

· Site preferences cookies - In order to remember your user preferences we need to set cookies so that this information can be called whenever you interact with a page that is affected by your preferences. 

#### Google Analytics

Google Analytics, which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solutions on the web for helping us understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content. The following resources are available for Google Analytics: [Privacy Policy](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage) and under [Terms of Service](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html). For more information, see the [Google Analytics Cookie Usage page](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage). 

We also use social media buttons and/or plugins on this site that allow you to connect with your social network in various ways. Facebook, Pinterest, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube, etc. For more information on their privacy policy, visit those sites for details. 

#### Email Newsletter

We use StreamSend.com for our weekly newsletter. Our newsletter contains tracking pixels (Newsletter-Tracking). A tracking pixel is a miniature graphic embedded in such e-mails, which are sent in HTML format to enable log file recording and analysis. This allows a statistical analysis of the success or failure of online marketing campaigns. Based on the embedded tracking pixel, SuncoastParts.com may see if and when an e-mail was opened and which links in the e-mail were clicked. Your personal data will not be passed on to third parties. We provide a single opt-in procedure as well as opting-out from our newsletters. If you elect to opt-out of our newsletter, your personal data will be removed and deleted. SuncoastParts.com automatically regards opting-out as a withdrawal from any further newsletters. 

#### Other Information

Every computer has an IP (Internet Protocol) address. IP addresses of computers used to visit this site are noted. In addition, we automatically collect other information such as email addresses, browser types, operating systems, and the URL addresses of sites clicked to and from this site. 

#### Information from Other Sources

We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. This may include updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

### How Do We Use Your Information?

#### Customized Shopping

We use your information to better serve you by providing a customized shopping experience. As noted above, you may “opt-out” of this customization, or even visit and shop anonymously.

#### Agents

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, and processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

#### Special Offers

We may send you special offers from time to time, unless you choose to “opt-out” of receiving such offers. In addition, we may also send you special offers from other companies. Again, you may “opt-out”. If we send you offers from other businesses, we do not share your personal information with them. The offers come directly through us. Please see the "opt-in/opt-out" selection at the end of this policy.

### How Do We Protect the Security of Your Information?

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 

We use encryption to protect your information contained in our customer list.

We use a firewall to protect against unlawful intrusion.

We limit access to your information on a "need to know" basis.

We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. 

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. No system can guarantee absolute security, just as the finest lock can not guarantee physical security. However, we take every reasonable precaution to assure that your data is secure.

### Your Choice: Opt-in or Opt-out

It is your choice whether to receive emails or special offers from us or others. The following section provides you with this choice. Please note the default settings.

Please send me email or other mail informing me of special offers of your products or services.

Please do not send me email or other mail informing me of special offers of your products or services.

Please send me email or other mail informing me of special offers of related products or services from other companies.

Please do not send me email or other mail informing me of special offers of related products or services from other companies.

### Children

We do not sell products or services to children. If you are under 18, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

### Other Websites

Various Web sites may be linked to from this site. If you link to another site, your privacy depends on the policy of that site. We strongly urge you to check their privacy policy. Not all sites guarantee that they will not share your personally identifiable information with others. You may also wish to consult privacy guidelines such as those recommended by the Online Privacy Alliance ([www.privacyalliance.org](http://www.privacyalliance.org/)). 

### Contact Us

If you would like to learn more about our privacy policy, or to access your personally identifiable information contained on our website, you may[ contact us](https://www.suncoastparts.com/Contact.html).

You will be required to provide identifier information to assure that this information is not released to others. We reserve the right to modify this policy in the future. If we do so, notice will be posted on our home page.
